[Chat with us](https://www.livechat.com/chat-with/7122941/), powered by [LiveChat](https://www.livechat.com/?welcome)             

X

Menu

Sign In

Close

Our Solutions* [Teachers2Parents](https://eduspot.co.uk/product/teachers2parents/)

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
==============

Eduspot has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our customers, candidates, and visitors to our site.

At Eduspot and our brands; Teachers2Parents, SchoolMoney, BehaviourWatch, SchoolPod and SchoolsWire, we are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect about users of our websites and is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Services.

This Privacy Policy also describes:

1. The measures we take to safeguard the information we collect.
2. Your rights and privileges concerning our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you.

Throughout this document, this website ([www.eduspot.co.uk](http://www.eduspot.co.uk/ "http://www.eduspot.co.uk")), and our affiliated products websites ([www.teachers2parents.co.uk](http://www.teachers2parents.co.uk/ "http://www.teachers2parents.co.uk"), [www.behaviourwatch.co.uk](http://www.behaviourwatch.co.uk/), [www.schoolmoney.co.uk](http://www.schoolmoney.co.uk/)) will be collectively referred to as the “Websites”. Services provided by or enabled via the websites will be referred to as the “Services”.

Please regularly review our Privacy Policy. By using our websites, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Websites.

Changes to the Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

The data Eduspot collects and uses is governed by this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time, not by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of data collection. This includes data collected from our websites, affiliates with links to this Privacy Policy, and services provided by or enabled via these sites.

Eduspot may change the Privacy Policy at our sole discretion and will provide notice of changes in the Privacy Policy and on the privacy policy page of our websites. If, as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which we can use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described in the section entitled “Privacy Rights”.

You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy after such notice has been posted with the following exception: If at the time you provide personal information to Eduspot you limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by Eduspot or by third parties, Eduspot will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent.

If Eduspot sells assets,  is acquired by or merged with another entity (or a division or subsidiary of), you agree that Eduspot may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold without obtaining your further consent. Eduspot will provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on our websites.

Policy Regarding Children
-------------------------

Eduspot websites and services are not designed for use by children under the age of 16. As such, our websites are not directed at children under the age of 16, nor do we knowingly collect or maintain information from children under the age of 16 on the websites.

Collection and Use of Data
--------------------------

Eduspot is the sole owner of the information collected on our websites. We have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, phone, surveys, forms or other direct contact from you.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We may disclose information to our corporate affiliates and third parties to provide products and services to you or in relation to products or services that you have purchased or downloaded from Eduspot.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about our services, new products, changes to this privacy policy or to provide you with information or educational newsletters.

If submitting any personal information about others, you represent and warrant that you are authorised to do so and that you have obtained the required consent to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

If applicable law allows you to supply the information without authorisation, you represent and warrant that you have abided by that law and that it allows us to receive and disclose the information under this Privacy Policy without any further action on our part. You agree to compensate, defend and hold harmless Eduspot, our parents, subsidiaries, officers, directors, employees, agents, sponsors, and supporting artists, licensors and suppliers for any failure by you to comply with this paragraph.

### Personal Information and Business Information

“Personal Information” as used in this Privacy Policy, is information that we directly associate with a specific person or entity, such as name, address, payment information, telephone number/s, and email address. Please note that any payment information we collect is not stored by us.

The Personal Information you provide will vary based on the context, and we will not collect your Personal Information unless you make it available. You are not required to provide Personal Information at any time while visiting our websites, however, you may be required to provide Personal Information to use certain Services.

You may provide us with Personal Information by participating in online surveys, subscribing to newsletters and other recurring offerings via our websites, and in connection with other products, services, features, or requests made available through our websites.

Eduspot collects the business information necessary to enable us to respond to your requests for our products and services and to send you information regarding our products and services from time to time. Since most of the users of our products and websites are doing so in their capacity as employees, schools or companies, the most business information we collect will be in that capacity (rather than information about you individually). For these purposes, we have defined “business information” as any information that identifies or may identify a school, company or an individual contact at a company or that allows others to contact a school, company or an individual contact at a company.

When you visit our websites, you may be asked to submit information such as e-mail address, company name, address, phone number, your product and/or areas of interest. We may also ask you where you heard about our company or products, or for other information that will help us understand more about your needs or help us process your requests for information.

### Support

We offer telephone and Email support services. If you access our support team, you may be asked for information such as organisation name, your name, contact number, contact email address, product name, and other information to help us determine what the queries are and how best to help you resolve them.

All support, sale or general enquiry calls and emails are recorded for training purposes, helping us to improve our services and products or to help resolve a query.

### Product-Related Information Collection

Eduspot collects certain additional information in connection with your use of our products and services with online features. For instance:

* **Online Product /Account Set-up:** Certain products and services are subject to a set-up and implementation process, which may be completed over the phone or online. Information requested may include bank account, payroll, credit card and contact information. This information is used to process your implementation request and, if approved, to set up and administrate your account.
* **Web-based Services:** Some of our web-based services collect certain additional information, including IP address, browser, connection speed, domain, referring URL and other environment-related information. This enables us to provide a secure environment for the use of the services, to pre-populate forms and calculate aggregate statistical information about the customers using these services. We use this information to better protect you and to provide a better user experience.

### Public Forums

Information (including personal and business information) that you submit, post or otherwise reveal in a public forum (such as comments to a blog or product discussion forum) is not subject to this Privacy Policy, will be seen by third parties not related to Eduspot and may be used by them or Eduspot to contact you for any purpose.

### Registrations

To access information (blogs, demos of our products, marketing materials etc.) on the websites or by email, a user may be required to register with Eduspot. During registration, a user is required to give certain information (such as name, email address, job title). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

### Sale of product

We request information from you when you purchase a product. To buy from us, you must provide contact information and on occasion specific financial information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your sale. If we have trouble processing a sale, we will use this information to contact you.

### Cookies

Eduspot may place “cookies” on the browser of your computer. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies may enhance the convenience and use of the website. For example, the information provided through cookies may be used to recognise you as a previous user of the website (so you do not have to enter your personal information every time), offer personalised information for your use, and otherwise, facilitate your experience using the website.

You may choose to decline cookies if your browser permits but doing so may affect your ability to access or use certain features of the website.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can disable this function so that your browser will not accept cookies. Please be aware that disabling this function may impact your use and enjoyment of this Website.

We utilise usage tracking cookies, such as Google Analytics and to offer surveys to our customers for us to better understand how our websites are used and to help us improve our services.

This data does not include personal information other than the IP address of your device. We may link an IP address to information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies For Remarketing

This website collects data for the purposes of running online remarketing campaigns on website visitors. By agreeing to this privacy policy, you are giving permission to serve ads based on your browsing history on this website.

Third-party vendors, such as Google, show our ads on websites across the internet.

Data is collected using Cookies. Cookies are used to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to a website.

The type of data collected and used for remarketing includes items such as the URL and referrer URL for the website that triggers a tag hit, the custom parameters used in your tracking tag and any resulting remarketing list memberships.

Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy, as well as Google’s policies.

Information about how visitors disable Google’s cookies can be found by [clicking here.](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop)

### Do Not Track

Currently, various browsers — including Microsoft Edge, Google Chrome, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, and Apple Safari — offer a “do not track” or “DNT” option that relies on a technology known as a DNT header, which sends a signal to websites visited by the user about the user’s browser DNT preference setting.  We do not currently commit to responding to browsers’ DNT signals with respect to the Company’s websites, in part, because no common industry standard for DNT has been adopted by industry groups, technology companies or regulators, including no consistent standard of interpreting user intent.

We take privacy and meaningful choice seriously and will make efforts to continue to monitor developments around DNT browser technology and the implementation of a standard.

Sub Processors
--------------

To be able to offer the best possible service, we take advantage of the best possible sub processors and technologies available, we undertake our own in depth Data Protection Assessment for each Sub-Processor we work with. A full list of our sub-processors can be found [here.](https://eduspot.co.uk/gdpr-statement/processors/)

Protecting Data During Collection
---------------------------------

We take precautions to protect and secure your information both online and offline when you submit sensitive information via the websites. These measures vary based on the sensitivity of the information that we collect, process and store.

Please be aware that no website or internet transmission is completely secure, so whilst we strive to protect your data, we cannot guarantee that unauthorised access, hacking, data loss or a data breach will never occur.

How We Use the Data We Collect
------------------------------

### Email Communication

Each email we send will contain instructions on how to unsubscribe should you decide not to receive future promotional e-mails. If you choose to opt-out from receiving promotional e-mail communications from any Eduspot business, we may still periodically communicate with you via mail and telephone.  Please allow up to 10 business days for your details to be removed from our promotional e-mail list.

Most of our communications are intended to:

* Inform you of product improvements and updates
* Inform you of regulatory and other compliance issues with your software product or service
* Notify you of products and services that we think may be of interest to you
* Offer you discounts or other promotions with respect to Eduspot products and services that we think may interest you
* Contact you for survey purposes to determine how we can improve our service to you or improve our products to better meet your needs

We send notification emails about the website and services from time to time as necessary. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

### Services and Product Data

Business Information collected by Eduspot as set forth in the _Personal Information and Business Information_ section above excludes data entered in the course of operating our products (“Product Data“) or data provided by you whilst using our services (“Services Data“). Eduspot will not access your Product Data or Services Data except in the following limited circumstances:

* To provide you with technical support, solely at your request and with your permission
* On a limited-access basis to install updates, produce regular backups or restore data from backups at your request
* Where the inherent purpose of the product or service requires Eduspot to provide the Product Data or Services Data to a third party on your behalf
* Unless you opt-out, to utilise aggregate Information derived from Product Data and Services Data to help us improve our products and services and in developing additional offerings. Aggregate Information is non-identifying information about you that is provided to third parties for analysis. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of users of this website and the activities they conduct while on this website to better understand user experience. Third-parties who receive aggregate information cannot identify or contact you based on the information they receive.

Eduspot will not provide your Product Data or Services Data to any third-party or permit any third-party to access your Product Data or Services Data, except with your permission or to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, or court order.

In addition, if at any time you decide to discontinue your use of the applicable product, your Services Data will be destroyed and removed from all servers according to terms set forth in your Master Agreement, subject to applicable back-up and disaster recovery practices and procedures.

Your personal information is stored on a secure server.

How We Share Data
-----------------

Unless you give us your permission, we don’t share data we collect from you with third parties, except as described below:

**Third-party service providers or consultants**. We may share data collected from you on the Eduspot site with third-party service providers or consultants who need access to the data to perform their work on Eduspot’s behalf, such as a website analytics company or a third-party advertising partner.

These third-party service providers are limited to only accessing or using this data to provide services to us and must provide reasonable assurances that they will appropriately safeguard the data.

**Compliance with Laws.** We may disclose your data to a third party if (i) we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request (including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements), (ii) to enforce our agreements and policies, (iii) to protect the security or integrity of the Eduspot Site or our services and products, (iv) to protect ourselves, our other customers, or the public from harm or illegal activities, or (v) to respond to an emergency which we believe in good faith requires us to disclose data to assist in preventing a death or serious bodily injury.

If Eduspot is required by law to disclose any of your data that directly identifies you, then we will use reasonable efforts to provide you with notice of that disclosure requirement, unless we are prohibited from doing so by statute, court or administrative order. Further, we object to requests that we do not believe were issued properly.

**Affiliates**. We may share data collected from you from the Eduspot site with our affiliates. We all will only use the data as described in this policy.

**Business Transfers**. If we go through a corporate sale, merger, reorganisation, dissolution or similar event, data we gather from you through our website may be part of the assets transferred or shared in connection with due diligence for any such transaction. Any acquirer or successor of Eduspot may continue to use the data we collect from you through our site as described in this policy.

**Aggregated or de-identified data**. We might also share data collected from you from the Eduspot site with a third party if that data has been de-identified or aggregated in a way that does not directly identify you.

We do not share your data (including, but not limited to, the personal data of your end users) with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you give us your consent to do so.

We may share certain personal information (for which we are a controller under applicable data protection laws) with our affiliates outside the UK including in the US where data protection laws are not deemed to have the same level of adequacy as in the UK or Europe in accordance with the lawful transfer mechanisms such as standard contractual clauses.

Privacy Rights
--------------

We may retain your information for a period of time, consistent with the original purpose of collection. For instance, we may retain your information during the time in which you have an account to use our websites, products or services and for a reasonable period of time afterward.

We also may retain your information during the period of time needed for us to pursue our legitimate business interests, conduct audits, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. Additionally, if the collection of your personal data was based on your consent, you have the right to revoke that consent at any time. Be aware that by revoking consent, you may lose access to services you previously opted to use.

You may request to review, correct, delete, or otherwise modify any of the personal information that you have previously provided to us through the company’s website/s, products, and services.

You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:

* See what data we have about you if any
* Change/correct any data we have about you
* Request for us to delete any data we have about you
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data

Requests to access, change, or delete your information will be addressed within a reasonable timeframe.

How to Contact Us
-----------------

Eduspot commits to resolve queries or complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. Eduspot takes its users’ privacy concerns seriously.

If you believe that Eduspot has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you should first contact us at Eduspot by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://eduspot.co.uk/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by writing to Eduspot at the following address:

Privacy – Eduspot  
2 Darker Street  
Leicester  
LE1 4SL  
United Kingdom

In your email or letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.

Please note that Eduspot is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Eduspot websites to which this site or any other Eduspot website may link. Also, Eduspot is not responsible for the privacy practices of its customers or users of its customer websites. You should review the additional privacy policy of the customer site before using the site.

Our Solutions

Company

Find Us At

Eduspot  
2 Darker Street  
Leicester  
LE1 4SL  
Telephone: 020 7237 8456

ICO Registration: Z3621757

Partners

[](tel:)[\[email protected\]](https://eduspot.co.uk/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Copyright © 2023 Eduspot. All rights reserved.
